finfacts.com 2006-06-29

# Finfacts Ireland Discliamer and Privacy Policy

If at any time after giving us personal information, you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use this information, or in the case that the information becomes out of date, you are free to notify us, and we will remove or rectify the information within a reasonable time. 

You acknowledge and agree that, in certain circumstances, we may be obliged to disclose personal information relating to you to third parties, for example, in order to conform to any requirements of law or to comply with any legal process, as well as to protect and defend the rights of property of Finfacts, our licensors and/or our other customers. 

Telephone calls may be monitored or recorded to ensure that we carry out your instructions correctly and to help improve the quality of our service.

**Use of Technical Information**

Cookies are files which are transferred to your computer's hard disk by a website. Cookies can store information about your preferences and other information which you need when you visit a website. Finfacts does not generally use cookies but these may be necessary in some parts of our website in order to provide you with certain features such as the customised delivery of certain information. To prevent the use of cookies, you should activate the facility, which is available in most web browsers that enables a user to deny or accept cookies.

Statistical and analytical information collected through the standard operation of our internet servers and logs provides us with general and not individually specific information. Finfacts will make no attempt to identify individual users, or to associate any technical information collected through the standard operation of our internet servers and logs with any individual user. 

**Disclaimer**  
Finfacts, its directors, employees, servants and agents, affiliates or other representatives and their respective parent and subsidiary companies, shall not be liable in respect of any claims, emergencies, demands, causes of action, damages, losses, expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable legal fees and costs of proceedings arising out of or in connection with the use and/or dissemination of personal information relating to you in accordance with this privacy policy and your consents. 

You should be aware that, where you link to another website from the Finfacts website, Finfacts has no control over that other website. Finfacts has no responsibility for the privacy practices of other websites.

While every effort is made to ensure that the information provided by Finfacts  on this Site, is accurate, all warranties whether express or implied, are disclaimed. Neither Finfacts, any member of the Company, nor suppliers of information, accept any responsibility for any loss or damage occasioned by any user of the finfacts.ie/com Site, whether through use of information provided by Finfacts or through access to other Internet Sites, facilitated by the finfacts.ie/com Site.

No liability is accepted in respect of any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential loss of business profits or special damages.

Access to and use of the finfacts.ie/com Site, is governed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Ireland and only the Courts of the Republic of Ireland shall have exclusive jurisdiction regarding any issues concerning the finfacts.ie/com Site **.**

**Amendments**

Finfacts reserves the right in its sole discretion to amend this privacy statement at any time, and you should regularly check this privacy statement for any amendments.

**Copyright**

The contents of the finfacts.ie/com Site are © Finfacts Multimedia Limited and remain at all times, the property of Finfacts Multimedia Limited.
